JOSE MARTOS

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, RWD, JavaScript, ES9, jQuery, Vue.js, Typescript, Mocha, Chai, Node.js, Express

Application Architecture, Webpack, Gulp, Parcel + Babel, PostCSS, ESlint, Prettier

Page optimization, SEO, JIRA, Git, Docker, Jenkins

COURSES

- React v16.8 (6h | 2019)
- Photoshop & Ilustrator CS5 (160h | 2012)
- Systems and networking (534h | 2006)

TOOLS

- VS Code, WebStorm, Sublime Text
- Invision, Zeplin, Avocode, Fireworks, Photoshop
- Sequel Pro, HeidiSQL, PhpMyAdmin, MySQL, Firebird

PERSONAL INTERESTS

Trekking, Traveling, Reading, Photography, Martial arts

CONTACT

martosjosele@gmail.com Based in Munich 10.07.1987 – Spain martosjose.com

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Developer with +9 years of experience. Eager for knowledge, creative and fast learner. Considers virtues such as politeness, code quality, punctuality, sense of humour, team work, problem-solving, reliability as well as proactivity vital within the working life. Looking for a suitable position in an already-stablished company, where to share and adquire new ideas, thoughts and abilities.

PROFESSIONAL CAREER

Front-end Developer

Pantaflix GmbH - Berlin (Mar 2017 - Sep 2018)

- Implemented a CMS tool for the customer care department using Vue.js, responsible for the set-up with Webpack and further development
- Responsible for the front-end on a CMS for filmmakers and users, using plain JavaScript and Twig
- Implemented new features on the main website, using jQuery and Node.js

Front-end Developer

Team2Venture GmbH - Berlin (Oct 2014 - Feb 2017)

- Participated in a CMS for external companies to handle freelancers and projects, using plain JavaScript and Scala templates
- Responsible for the development of a hybrid mobile app, using AngularJS
- Implemented new features on the main website, participating on a migration from Backbone and RequireJS to plain JavaScript and Browserify + Gulp

Full-stack Developer

Dreamsite - Madrid (Jun 2012 - Sep 2014)

- Developed +15 corporation websites
- Integrated designs in Wordpress pages
- Managed and updated websites, applications and already implemented tools

Junior Full-stack Developer

Uniagro SL - Málaga (Jul 2009 - May 2012)

- Designed and developed +25 corporation websites
- Designed logos and banners
- Managed and updated websites, applications and already implemented tools

EDUCATION

Senior Technician in Computer Applications Development (2007 - 2009) IES Pedro Espinosa, Antequera, Málaga

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native | English: C1 | German: B1